They're not the same, are they?
它们不一样，不是吗？
The smiles you see when you meet your friends and family compared with what you see from salespeople trying to get you to buy something or management consultants pretending that the bad news they're giving you is actually good news.
你看到的朋友和家人脸上的笑容，与那些试图让你买东西的销售人员，或者假装通知的坏消息实际上是好消息的管理顾问脸上的笑容是不同的。
How can we tell that someone really means it when they're smiling?
我们如何判断别人微笑时是否是真心实意的？
There are physical differences between types of smiles.
不同类型的微笑之间存在生理差异。
19th Century French neurologist, Guillaume Duchenne, spotted that there are two sets of muscles that are used for smiling.
19世纪法国神经学家纪尧姆·杜兴发现，微笑使用两组肌肉。
Unsurprisingly, one set of muscles moves the corners of your mouth.
不出所料，一组肌肉移动嘴角。
The other tightens the skin around your eyes.
另一组则收紧眼周的皮肤。
He noticed that only genuine smiles triggered the muscles around the eyes, leading a real smile to be named a Duchenne smile.
他注意到，只有真诚的微笑才会触发眼周肌肉，因此真诚的微笑被称为"杜兴微笑"。
Later research suggests that there are two pathways to triggering these sets of muscles.
后来的研究表明，触发这些肌肉有两条途径。
Those that are around the mouth can be set off voluntarily, while those around the eyes are triggered involuntarily and almost always by our emotions.
嘴部周围的肌肉可以随意触发，而眼周的肌肉则是不由自主地触发的，几乎总是由我们的情绪引发。
A genuine smile has certain physical signs.
真诚的微笑有一定的生理迹象。
Typically, if a smile is real, then people's cheeks are pulled up, the skin under their eyes bulges, and crow's feet can be seen at the corners of their eyes.
通常，如果微笑是真实的，那么人的脸颊会上提，眼下皮肤会鼓起，眼角可以看到鱼尾纹。
Smiles that aren't genuine often disappear suddenly rather than fading gradually.
不真诚的微笑往往会突然消失，而不是逐渐消退。
These fake smiles are not caused by emotions, but they can get mixed with signs of the emotions that someone is genuinely feeling, like a wrinkled forehead caused by worry.
这些假笑并非由情绪引起，但它们可能与某人真实感受到的情绪迹象混杂在一起，比如因担忧而皱起的额头。
Even ten-month-old-babies have shown that they can identify a real smile.
即使是十个月大的婴儿也能辨别出真诚的微笑。
It may be that we have evolved to spot genuine emotion.
有可能我们已经进化出识别真实情感的能力。
There's clearly a benefit in being able to identify who to trust, and who may be trying to deceive us.
能够识别谁值得信任、谁可能在试图欺骗我们，肯定是有益的。
That's not to say that fake smiles are always a problem.
这并不是说假笑总是个问题。
They can help to smooth over difficult situations and maintain politeness.
它们有助于缓和尴尬局面并保持礼貌。
But there are times when it's good to know that a smile really means something.
但有些时候，知道一个微笑确实意味着什么，是件好事。